{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"2666","name":"Kentucky Fried Chicken","address":"14201 W Seven Mile Rd","zipcode":"48235","owner":"FQSR LLC DBA KBP FOODS","licenseNumber":"202821","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","coords":"-83.18557,42.43042","geojson":{"id":"2666","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.1855692459999,42.4304227710001]},"properties":{"name":"Kentucky Fried Chicken","owner":"FQSR LLC DBA KBP FOODS","address":"14201 W Seven Mile Rd","zipcode":"48235","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"202821","establishmentid":"2666","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"180.0","most_recent_license_date":"3/29/2018"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"1352","name":"McDonald's #7025","address":"14204 W Seven Mile Rd","zipcode":"48235"},{"establishmentid":"4622","name":"Subway 51089","address":"19100 James Couzens","zipcode":"48235"},{"establishmentid":"2664","name":"Wendy's Old Fashioned Hamburgers #8633","address":"14401 W Seven Mile Rd","zipcode":"48235"},{"establishmentid":"3786","name":"Hartford Memorial Baptist Church","address":"18700 James Couzens","zipcode":"48235"},{"establishmentid":"5221","name":"Captain Jay's #119","address":"14420 Seven Mile Rd W","zipcode":"48235"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"44390","inspectionDate":"2018-11-29T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"7-204.11","violationDescription":"Chemical SANITIZERS and other chemical antimicrobials applied to FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES shall meet the requirements specified in this code. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Sanitizer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Do not comply with law","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-11-29T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove and replace to be in compliance with law."},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean prior to opening"},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"SELF-SERVE (POP STATION)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"42868","inspectionDate":"2018-07-11T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-901.11","violationDescription":"After cleaning and SANITIZING, EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS shall be air-dried or used after adequate draining.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Clean equipment and utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored/stacked wet","subProblem":"","location":"STORAGE AREA (DRY)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Completely air dry all items prior to storage/use."}]},{"inspectionid":"40251","inspectionDate":"2017-10-04T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"6-501.14","violationDescription":"(A) Intake and exhaust air ducts shall be cleaned and filters changed so they are not a source of contamination by dust, dirt, and other materials. \r\n(B) If vented to the outside, ventilation systems may not create a public health HAZARD or nuisance or unLAWful discharge.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Ventilation system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"VENTILATION HOOD SYSTEM","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"}]},{"inspectionid":"38300","inspectionDate":"2017-02-10T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"2-301.14","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall clean their hands and exposed portions of their arms as specified under § 2-301.12 immediately before engaging in FOOD preparation including working with exposed FOOD, clean EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, and unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES (P) and:\r\n(A)     After touching bare human body parts other than clean hands and clean, exposed portions of arms; (P)\r\n(B)     After using the toilet room; (P)\r\n(C)     After caring for or handling SERVICE ANIMALS or aquatic animals as specified in ¶ 2-403.11(B); (P).\r\n(D)     Except as specified in ¶ 2-401.11(B), after coughing, sneezing, using a handkerchief or disposable tissue, using tobacco, eating, or drinking; (P)\r\n(E)     After handling soiled EQUIPMENT or UTENSILS; (P)\r\n(F)     During FOOD preparation, as often as necessary to remove soil and contamination and to prevent cross contamination when changing tasks; (P)\r\n(G)     When switching between working with raw FOOD and working with READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\r\n(H)     Before donning gloves for working with FOOD; (P) and\r\n(I)      After engaging in other activities that contaminate the hands. (P)","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Employee(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Did not wash hands","subProblem":"after other activities","location":"EMPLOYEE(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-02-10T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Hands shall be washed with hot water and soap for at least 20 seconds after contamination."},{"violationCode":"6-201.11","violationDescription":"Except otherwise approved, and except for antislip floor coverings or applications may be used for safety reasons, floors, floor coverings, walls, wall coverings, and ceilings shall be designed, constructed, and installed so they are SMOOTH and EASILY CLEANABLE.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Floor(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not smooth and easily cleanable","subProblem":"","location":"FLOOR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be smooth."},{"violationCode":"6-501.16","violationDescription":"After use, mops shall be placed in a position that allows them to air-dry without soiling walls, EQUIPMENT, or supplies.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Wet mop(s) storage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Allows for contamination","subProblem":"","location":"MOP SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-02-10T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove to prevent contamination."}]},{"inspectionid":"36455","inspectionDate":"2016-09-14T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Reach-in Freezer","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/Replace"}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"2666"}}